(self.webpackChunk_N_E=self.webpackChunk_N_E||[]).push([[738],{9857:function(e,s,a){"use strict";a.r(s),a.d(s,{default:function(){return r}});var t=a(9008),i=a(7294),n=[{question:"ERROR EPERM BLEH BLEH BLEH BLEH BLEH BLEH BLEH BLEH Lorem Ipsum Dolor Sit Amet Consectetur Adipiscing Elit Mattis Eros Vivamus Euismod Nisl Quisque BLEH BLEH BLEH BLEH",answers:["vinayak kjashfkjdhsfkjhdkjshfkjdhsfkjhdskfjh","sarthak lkdfjklsjfkldjasfkl","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how buidl the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"093909"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"009039"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"090089"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"01010101"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"092299"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"2222099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09922099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"222292099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0998999099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"099099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"09459099"},{question:"how build the app ?",answers:["vinayak","sarthak","somil","devesh"],correct:"vinayak",questionId:"0912219099"}],o=a(5893),r=function(){var e=(0,i.useState)(0),s=e[0],a=e[1],r=new Map;return(0,o.jsxs)("div",{children:[(0,o.jsxs)(t.default,{children:[(0,o.jsx)("title",{children:"Quests"}),(0,o.jsx)("meta",{name:"description",content:"Quest Topics"})]}),(0,o.jsx)("div",{className:"flex justify-center h-full w-full",children:(0,o.jsx)("div",{className:"flex w-3/4 h-full justify-evenly bg-black bg-opacity-50 backdrop-blur-xl rounded-lg drop-shadow-lg text-white m-5 rounded",children:(0,o.jsxs)("div",{className:"flex flex-col justify-center items-center p-3",children:[(0,o.jsx)("div",{className:"text-xl font-bold mb-3",children:"Quest"}),(0,o.jsxs)("div",{className:"w-full flex flex-col justify-center items-start border border-gray-300 rounded-lg",children:[(0,o.jsx)("div",{className:"text-xl text-white font-bold m-10",children:n[s].question}),(0,o.jsx)("div",{className:"text-md flex flex-col mx-10 mb-16 gap-3",children:n[s].answers.map((function(e,a){return(0,o.jsxs)("div",{className:"text-lg flex flex-row justify-start items-center gap-3",children:[(0,o.jsx)("input",{type:"radio",name:"answer",className:"answerBtn custom-radio",id:"outline",value:e,title:e,onClick:function(){console.log(e),r.set(s,e),console.log(r.get(s))}},a),(0,o.jsx)("div",{children:e})]})}))}),(0,o.jsxs)("div",{className:"w-full text-md text-white  flex flex-row justify-evenly",children:[(0,o.jsx)("button",{className:"backBtn p-3 text-xl w-1/3 bg-[#e42103a1] hover:bg-[#e42103] rounded-bl-lg",onClick:function(){return a(s-1)},children:"<\xa0\xa0\xa0\xa0 Prev"}),(0,o.jsx)("button",{className:"answerBtn p-3 text-xl w-2/3 bg-[#03a0e4b5] hover:bg-[#04adc4] rounded-br-lg",onClick:function(){return a(s+1)},children:s<n.length-1?"Submit":"Finish"})]})]})]})})})]})}},606:function(e,s,a){(window.__NEXT_P=window.__NEXT_P||[]).push(["/quests",function(){return a(9857)}])}},function(e){e.O(0,[774,888,179],(function(){return s=606,e(e.s=s);var s}));var s=e.O();_N_E=s}]);